《老爸们》在录影棚现场录制
Dads is recorded in front of a live studio audience.
哇  网球电子游戏
Wow, video game tennis.
我还真不知道自己儿子简直就是个假装的运动天才
I had no idea my son was such a gifted fake athlete.
我们得好好练习
We got to practice.
我们要组队参加SFVTT比赛
We're partners in the SFVTT.
我已经兴趣全无了
I already don't care what it is.
就是旧金山虚拟网球公开赛
It's the San Francisco Virtual Tennis Tournament
兴趣全无就对了
I was right not to care.
- 嘿  David  - 嘿  Crawford
- Hey, David.  - Hey, Crawford.
Camila  两杯马丁尼
Camila, two martinis.
我不喝
I don't need one.
我知道
I know.
你能相信这些荒谬的话么?
Can you believe this nonsense?
咱们还小的时候  真是实实在在地做一些事情的
When we were kids, you actually did things.
你想要打网球  那就去打网球
You wanted to play tennis, you played tennis.
是啊  那时候我们没有计算机
Well, and we didn't have computers then,
而且基本上那个时候想看女生内裤就只能去看她们打网球
so basically tennis was the only way to see women's underwear.
是电子游戏让这个国家一塌糊涂
Video games are why this country's going to hell.
我像他那么大的时候都已经成家立业了
By the time I was his age, I already had a family
然后撇家舍业
and left them.
我正和最好的朋友一起玩得高兴呢
Look, I'm having fun with my best friend.
那可是你从没体会过的
That's an experience you've never had.
我有很多朋友
I got friends.
不  你没有
No, you don't.
除了Crawford以外你再说一个你朋友的名字
Name me one friend you've got besides Crawford.
Edna.
我的保姆?
My maid?
她姓什么?
What's her last name?
好吧  败给你了
All right, you got me.
可我要是想交朋友就是分分钟的事情
But I could make friends in two seconds.
你怎么交朋友?
How could you make friends?
或许你碰上飞机失事然后幸存下来
M-Maybe if you were in a plane crash and survived,
就能有几个同样诡异的难友了
you could have weird survival friends,
要是没有遇到飞机失事
but there is no way
你就绝不可能在正常情况下
that you could have personality-based friends
凭自己人品交到朋友
in a non-plane-crash setting.
伙计  要是咱们都是摩门教徒交朋友就容易多了
[Mormons:摩门教  泛基督信仰宗派运动的一个分支  倡导一夫多妻制]
Boy, it'd be so much easier to make friends if we were Mormons.
很可能我们得和18个兄弟姐妹睡一间卧室
We'd have 18 brothers and sisters right in the bedroom.
老爸们  第一季  第八集
天天美剧字幕组 www.ttmeiju.com
本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业用途
翻译: 水果虫虫  大Z  狗娃子  紫陌
校对: 兰陵笑笑生
不错  穿着睡衣的时候
Yep, scotch definitely tastes better
还是喝苏格兰威士忌更带劲
when you're wearing pajamas.
不管是睡前最后一杯
Whether it's that last one at night
还是起床第一杯
or that first one in the morning.
Eli说你是他最好的朋友的时候
That was pretty cute
Eli真是太可爱了
when Eli said you were his best friend.
是啊
Yeah.
他是个可爱的孩子
He's a cute kid.
那他是你最好的朋友么?
Is he your best friend?
当然不是了  亲爱的
Course not, honey.
然后呢...
And...
你才是
You are.
很好  因为我正想着  今年应该由我和你组队
Good. 'Cause I was thinking I could be your teammate this year
去参加那个网球公开赛
in the tennis tournament.
我不能这么对Eli的  他是我最好的朋友
I can't do that to Eli. He's my best friend.
我们从来都没有一起参加过什么活动
We have no activities together.
你在说什么啊?  我们不是一直花很多时间
What are you talking about? We take long, silent car rides
一起安静地坐车么
together all the time.
Eli就找不到其他的搭档了么?
Can't Eli just find another partner?
你懂的  红头发很难交到朋友
Well, you know, it's hard for redheads to make friends.
因为人们总是下意识地觉得他们是恶魔投胎
'Cause people subconsciously think they're evil.
好吧  我去自己那张单人对床睡觉了
Well, I am off to my twin bed.
晚安了夫人
Say good night to the missus.
亲爱的  夫妻总是在一起做很多事情的
Honey, couples do things together all the time.
Jen和Bob一起去打高尔夫
Jen and Bob play golf.
因为他劈腿了所以内心有愧
Well, that's because he feels bad for cheating on her.
Zack和Beth一起唱卡拉OK
Zack and Beth have karaoke.
那是因为Zack和Bob勾搭上了所以心虚
That's because Zack feels bad for hooking up with Bob.
Lucas和Moira一起去攀岩
Lucas and Moira go rock climbing.
他是想趁机干掉她
But he's trying to kill her.
他会把绳子切断的
He's-he's gonna cut the rope.
报纸头版就等着刊登这条了
It's a Dateline waiting to happen.
说真的呢  宝贝  咱们一起做了什么啊?
Seriously, baby, what do we do together?
我们...  我们在谈论其他夫妻啊
We-we talk about other couples.
好吧  我只是觉得...
All right. I just thought...
要是咱们一起干点什么会很开心的  但是...
it would be something fun for us to do together, but...
我想...
I guess...
是我错了
I was wrong.
哦  别这样
Oh, come on.
别发出那么沮丧的走路声
Not the sad walk.
我才不会那么轻易上当呢
It's not... I'm not gonna fall for it.
不  不不  这次不会
Nah, n-no. Not this time.
不会
No.
你怎么了?
What's wrong?
哦没什么  我就是在纠结怎么告诉Eli
Oh, nothing. I'm just trying to figure out a way to tell Eli
Camila要跟我一队打网球
that Camila's my new tennis partner.
那你准备说些什么呢?
Oh, how are you gonna do that?
嗯  我写了点东西  想着...
Well, I-I wrote some stuff down that maybe I could...
-念给我听听  -好吧...
- Go for it.  - Okay, uh...
首先  我说我很爱他这个朋友
First, how much I-I love him as a friend
也很珍惜跟他之间的合作关系  呃...
and I value his partnership. Uh...
然后  我加了一个小笑话
next, I slipped in a little joke.
接着  呃  我回忆和他度过的美好时光
And then I, uh, reminded him of the good times we had together,
然后是另一则更小的笑话...
then a second smaller joke, this and that...
最后  告诉他这个坏消息  沉重的打击
and then, uh, I hit him hard with the bad news,
可我不知道怎么当面跟他说
but I just don't think I can say it to his face.
那你发短信好了
So text him.
啊?  我怎么能发短信呢
Really? I can't text him.
那也太懦弱了吧  这可不行  太蠢了...
That's so cowardly. I mean, come on. That's ridi...
啊  他来了
Oh, here he is.
发送
And send.
大家好啊
Hey, guys.
唉呦
Aw.
的确是美好时光啊
It was good times.
没有第一个好笑  不过也不错
Not as good as the first one but still-still funny.
等一下
One second.
我没明白
I didn't get it.
啊  我发给Edna了
Oh, I sent it to Edna.
伙计  这可不地道
Not cool, man.
Eli  你想放在哪儿?
Where do you want this, Eli?
噢
Oh.
很好
Perfect.
别这样
Come on.
也太傻了
This is ridiculous.
我们可是最好的朋友  跟我说话啊
We're best friends. Talk to me.
全都倒过来了
It's upside down.
不对啊  是正的
No, it's not.
听着  我知道你很失望
Look, I know you're really disappointed,
可我老婆想跟我一队
but my wife wants to be my tennis partner
她最重要嘛
[也有"她先高潮的意思"]
and she comes first.
不对  我不是这意思
Well, not in that way.
嗯  有时确实有这种情况
Well, okay, sometimes.
好吧  只有一次啦  我完全不知道自己做了什么
Okay, once and I still have no idea what I did.
听着  我知道你想跟Camila一起做一些有意思的事
Look, I know you want to do fun stuff with Camila,
可虚拟网球是属于咱俩的啊
but virtual tennis was ours.
要是我跑到你们家
How would she like it if I went to your house
帮你熨衣服  生小孩  她会怎么想
and ironed your clothes and had your kids?
估计她会觉得非常  非常困扰
I think she'd be very, very confused.
我现在就很困扰好吗
I'm very confused right now.
我连我的名字是啥都不知道了
I don't even know my own name!
你的名字是Eli
It's Eli.
这话听起来真不对劲
That doesn't sound right.
你想躺下平静一下吗
Do you want to lie down right now?
不想
No.
我要再找个队友
I want to find another partner.
很好  这就对了  Eli
Well, okay. That's the spirit, Eli.
可我不知道找谁啊
I don't know who that is!
对  不不不  Jeff
Yeah. No, no, no, Jeff.
我能理解
I totally understand.
那你化疗做完了以后还有事吗
Hey, what are you doing after chemo?
好吧
Fine.
现在的人真自私
People are so selfish!
看来你的朋友都很挺你嘛
So, all your friends coming through for you?
现在可不是嘲笑我的时候  老爸
Not now, Dad.
《荒岛余生》这部电影说得对
The movie Castaway got it right.
朋友嘛  都可以用充气球来代替
Friends can be replaced by an inflatable ball.
知道吗  我刚被最好的朋友甩了
You know, I just lost my actual best friend.
我很需要别人的支持
I could use a little bit of support.
世界上就没有"最好的朋友"这回事
There's no such thing as a best friend.
甚至狗都不能成为你最好的朋友
Even dogs aren't your best friends.
你在说什么啊?
What are you talking about?
如果你死在家里了  要不了24小时
If you were to die in you apartment, within 24 hours,
你所谓的"最好的朋友"就会开始啃你的脸
your "best friend" would be eating your face.
还记得你是怎么五年如一日的跟在他屁股后面捡便便的吗?
Remember how you picked up his poop for five years?
他早忘的一干二净了
He doesn't.
他嘴里咬着你的耳朵
He's got your ear in his mouth,
摇着尾巴  正享受呢
tail wagging, having a grand old time.
老爸  如果你真想帮忙
Dad, if you really want to help me,
你可以跟我组队参加网球比赛啊
maybe you can be my partner in this tennis tournament.
如果我的个性里有那么一小部分
If there's anything in my personality that has given rise
让你觉得我愿意帮你
to the belief that I would help you with this,
我真心地抱歉
I truly apologize.
David先生  这很简单
It's easy, Mr. David.
就像用鸡毛掸子扫灰
Like feather duster.
左拍拍  右拍拍
Feather, dust. Feather, dust.
前扫扫  后扫扫
Feather, dust. Feather, dust
天啊
Oh, my God.
Edna  你太棒了
E-Edna, you're amazing.
等等  你明天有空吗?
Wait, a-are you busy tomorrow?
我每天花八小时打扫两间屋子
I spend eight hours a day cleaning two rooms.
当然有时间
Yeah, I got time.
好吧
Well, here it is,
重在参与一代人的“超级碗”
the Super Bowl of the participation ribbon generation.
你猜我最喜欢看谁的网球比赛?
You know who I love to watch play tennis?
Wiliams两哥们
[Williams brothers: 吐槽大威和小威健硕的身材...]
Those Williams brothers.
叹为观止
Amazing.
现在
And now,
进行我们今天的决赛
for our final match of the day,
Warner and Camila Whittemore
对阵Eli和Edna
versus Eli and Ed-na...!
哦  这位就是久闻大名的女士
Oh. So, this is the other woman I've been hearing so much about.
Eli  我已经认识你15年了
Eli, I've known you for 15 years.
- 是吗?  那我还认识他25年了呢  - 好了好了
- Yeah? Well, I've known him for 25.  - Okay,
同志们  这又不是什么竞技比赛
guys, this is not a competition.
现在比赛正式开始
The competition will now begin.
Whittemore队发球
Team Whittemore to serve.
Edna队率先得分  15比0
Point, Edna. Love-15.
- 抱歉  - 没事的
- Sorry. I'm so sorry.  - It's okay.
你做得很好
It's okay, you're doing great.
- 你做得很好  好吗?  - 好的
- Okay? You're doing great.  - Okay.
看看那些美腿
Would you look at those legs!
那当然  我们Whittemore家的男人以美腿著名
Yeah, we Whittemore men are known for our great legs.
想当年我穿着超短裤
You know, once I was wearing short shorts
在纽约街上压马路
in New York City...
两辆的士正好开在人行道上
and two cabs just drove right up on the sidewalk.
其中一辆撞上了消防栓  五分钟之后
One of them hit a fire hydrant, and five minutes later,
街道就变成有色人种的水上乐园了
it was an ethnic water park.
ELi和Edna率先拿下第一局
Game and first set, Eli and Edna!
好耶!
Yeah!
搭档选的不错啊  兄弟
Oh, great partner choice, buddy.
你需要你振作起来  好吗?
Look, I need you to pick it up, all right?
你想做我的搭档  那就加油  好吗?
You wanted to be partner, so let's go, all right?
我爱你  爱你爱你爱你
I love you. Love, love, love.
爱昵
Love, love, love. Love.
你们怎么认识Edna的?
How do you know Edna?
Edna是谁?
Who's Edna?
我们刚才Dane Cook秀回来
[Dane Cook:  美国著名脱口秀和喜剧演员]
We just came from a Dane Cook show.
秀怎么样?
How was it?
无聊透了
It sucked.
Eli和Edna拿下赛点
Match point, Eli and Edna.
亲爱的  我们只需要
All right, honey, we just need to win
- 连赢212分  好吗?  - 好的
- 212 points in a row, okay?  - Okay.
- 加油?  - 加油
- Okay?  - Okay.
Eli和Edna  模拟网球比赛冠军!
Eli and Edna are your virtual tennis champions!
她作弊  她嗑类固醇了!
She cheated!  She's on steroids!
好了  别这样  哥们  放轻松
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, come on, dude, relax.
喔  真是不错的建议
Oh, yeah! Great advice!
那就是你咯?
That's you, isn't it?
放轻松先生
Mr. Relaxed.
从来工作上不犯错
Never doing anything at work.
我穿着t恤酷毙了
Hey, I'm really cool 'cause I'm wearing a T-shirt
想不到我40了吧
and I'm 40 years old.
行了  Wener
Okay, Werner,
天啦  给我停下
stop it! Oh, my gosh,
别再丢人现眼了
you are making a fool of yourself right now.
我 我在丢人现眼?
I-I'm making a fool of myself?!
- 亲爱的 是你把最后一球搞砸了吧  - 我没有
You totally blew that last shot, honey.  - No.
我差点就接到球了  但你把我推开了
I almost got that last shot, but you pushed me out of the way.
那就是你要击到的球?
Oh! Was that the one shot you were gonna make?
天了噜  你压根就没接到任何球  你知道吗?
Yay! You didn't make one! You know what?
尽力就足够了的话
'Cause almost is good enough.
那Jar Jar Binks还近乎有趣
[Jar Jar Binks:  星战人物  就是那个突眼镜兔耳朵长舌头的刚噶族人]
And Jar Jar Binks was almost funny.
那美国还差点打赢了越南战争
And America almost won Vietnam!
我们就来庆祝咯?
Hey, let's celebrate, huh?
别盯着我看
Don't look at me.
事实上  如果按死了的人数算
Well, you know, if you go by body count,
我们确实赢了越南
we did win the Vietnam War.
谁先开始讲?
So, who wants to start?
我觉得Warner应该先来
Uh, well, I think Warner should start.
附议
Yeah, me, too.
Warner  你为什么今天会来这儿
Warner, why do you think you're all here today?
那是因为
Uh... 'cause...
因为我有点生气
'cause I got a little upset.
- 有点生气  - 是啊
- A little upset?  - Yeah.
你把我跟加加宾克斯比[注: 星战人物 外星人]
You compared me to Jar Jar Binks.
是啊 你还摔了个电视机
Yeah, and you smashed a TV.
那是个希望工程学校电视 拜托
That was an inner-city school, man.
他们不可能再找到第二个那样的了
They're not gonna get another one of those.
Warner 你能解释你的愤怒是从哪里来的吗
Warner, can you explain where your anger came from,
为什么你觉得有必要用大动干戈的形式表达它?
why you felt the need to manifest it physically?
额...
Uh...
不能
no.
或许这跟现实状况有关
Maybe it has something to do with the fact
因为你的老婆不尊重我们的友谊
that your wife doesn't respect our friendship.
或许是因为你最好的朋友没有意识到
Maybe it's because your best friend doesn't realize
你的妻子和孩子需要你
your wife and children need you.
需要他?!  更像是需要安抚他
Need him?! More like need to smother him.
那你总是需要让他加班的呢
What about your need to keep him working late
所以你可以有人陪着看傻瓜电影的暗喻一起笑
so you have someone around to laugh at your dumb movie references.
吾以地狱之名戳死汝
From hell's heart I stab at thee!
- 可汗之怒（星战II）  - 谢谢
- Wrath of Khan.  - Thank you.
那又怎样
So what?
我是他的妻子
I'm his wife.
是啊 我看到他的裸体比你早
Yeah, I saw him naked before you did.
在你们的关系里有关性的因素吗
Is there a sexual element to this relationship?
- 不  - 不
- No.  - No.
好吧 可能这就是问题所在
Well, maybe that's the problem.
- 不  - 不
- No.  - No.
你知道不 我今天听到很多个不
You know, I'm hearing a lot of "no,"
这让我觉得语言可能无法表达我们的真实内心
which makes me think that words may be failing us here.
跟我来
Come with me.
好吧
Okay.
哦
Oh.
这好酷
This is cool.
嘿  你常开趴?
Hey, do you party?
这是我们的无语言交流室
This is our nonverbal communication room.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
它让你释放你的情绪
It allows you to express your emotions
用纯的声音
using the pure truth of sound.
是的  你常开趴
Yeah, you party.
请
Please.
所以  额
So, uh...
我我们随便选个鼓还是怎样...?
w-we just choose a drum or what...?
鼓会选择你们
The drum will choose you.
好吧 随便选一个
All right, just pick one.
现在让我开始对话
Now let me start the conversation.
安静!
Eli  你是我最好的兄弟
我知道
亲爱的  我对你的爱无以复加
谢谢亲爱的
你真美
知道你喜欢这件T恤我才穿的
每次看着你
我都感觉
三生有幸
我想舔你脖子
开脱吧？
伙计们
我还在呢
把你名字写我背上！
太黄不翻译
咱俩来一发?
我可是会教你点姿势
不
No.
把鼓放下
Put the drum down.
我做不到
I can't.
你想晚上出去玩吗
You want to hang out tonight?
好吧 我想和你出去玩
Well, I would love to hang out with you,
因为你是个很好的朋友我很珍惜我们一起的时光
because you are a great friend and I value our time together...
...但是我跟Camila有计划了
...but I'm doing something with Camila,
她也是个很好的朋友
who's also a great friend,
一个慷慨的爱人
and a generous lover.
我听到你这么说十分欣慰
I am so glad to hear that.
当我觉得我不能看到你而沮丧的时候
And while I am disappointed that I won't get to see you,
我很感激你跟我交流了你的计划
I appreciate you communicating your plan to me.
好吧...
Well...
交流是是一段强大友谊的基础
communication is the basis for a strong friendship.
也正是我们俩现在拥有的
Which is what we have.
友谊万岁
To friendship
到底在干吗呢?
What the hell is going on?
好吧 Eli和我正在心理疗程中解决一些问题
Well, Eli and I worked some stuff out in therapy.
你应该试试 额
You should try it. Ugh,
不可能  亚洲人不相信心理疗程
no way... Asians don't believe in therapy.
我们有个情绪开关
We have on-off switches.
哦 我想要了解更多
Oh. I'd like to hear more about this.
你今晚有空吗
Are you free tonight?
然后关掉了
And off.
所以  跟Camila一切安好?
So, things good with Camila?
哦 是的 我们昨晚大干了一场
Oh, yeah, we made up big-time last night.
这次她给我拿了毛巾
This time she brought me the towel.
她真是个慷慨的爱人
She is such a generous lover.
是啊
Yeah.
你昨晚跟心理医生怎么样了
How did things end up with you and the therapist?
所以她不打算起诉你?
So she's not pressing charges?
你必须一直跟她保持100码距离?
You have to stay a hundred yards away at all times?
哦 50 好的 很好 是的
Oh, 50. Okay, nice, yeah.
你们俩
You guys,
拜托  哦!
come on! Oh!
你准备好泰格伍兹附身上阵了吗?!
Are you ready to get your Tiger Woods on?!
是的  他是最好的墨西哥高尔夫手
Sí-. He best Mexican golfer ever.
不 额  泰格伍兹是黑人加亚裔
No, uh, Tiger Woods is black plus Asian.
是  那就是墨西哥人!
Sí-. Equal Mexican!
欢迎加入天天美剧字幕组
@天天美剧
www.ttmeiju.com